{
  "chapter": 6,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the organization majorly helping to foster security standards for cloud computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "NIST",
        "Cloud Security WatchDog",
        "Cloud Security Alliance",
        "Open Cloud Consortium"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "‘Perimeter’ in the peremeterized computing environment is represented by",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Organization’s physical boundary",
        "In-house data center boundary",
        "IP addresses",
        "Network firewalls"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "On how many elements of cloud security model it was focused in Gartner’s report titled as ‘Assessing the Security Risks of Cloud Computing’ published in 2008?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["6", "7", "8", "None of these"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who proposed the globally-accepted model for cloud security?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cloud Security Alliance",
        "Jericho Forum group",
        "NIST",
        "Object Management Group (OMG)"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Into how many visible cubes, the model cube was divided in Jericho Forum’s security model?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["8", "16", "4", "32"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many dimensions exist in Cloud Cube Model?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among of the following security policies demands special attention in cloud computing?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data security policy",
        "Security management policy",
        "Advisory policy",
        "Regulatory policy"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among of the four dimensions of the cloud cube model is represented by the colour?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data Boundary",
        "Ownership",
        "Security Boundary",
        "Sourcing"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "De-perimeterization in computing promotes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Outsourcing",
        "Use of open technology",
        "Collaboration",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "The statement ‘Internal data source can be used in de-perimeterized computing environment’ is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "In traditional perimeterized computing environment, collaboration with external systems are established through",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Virtual private network technique",
        "Virtual drive technique",
        "De-perimeterization technique",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
